{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Mudjackers \u0026 Concrete Leveling Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40195/":{"taskOID":40195,"originalTaskOID":40195,"setID":502,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7044,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the location of the concrete leveling project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10540,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Finish floor in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Finish floor in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10541,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Subflooring in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Subflooring in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10542,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage or basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage or basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10543,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10544,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exterior walkway/patio","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway/patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10545,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10546,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4053,"questionDisplayText":"Damage Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the damage to your concrete?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2972,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Heaving","answerDisplayText":"Heaving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5593,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Settling","answerDisplayText":"Settling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1702,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cracking","answerDisplayText":"Cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4054,"questionDisplayText":"Special Applications","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Does the concrete being repaired have any special applications or finishes?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5930,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","answerDisplayText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3607,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lightweight concrete","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2303,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exposed aggregate finish","answerDisplayText":"Exposed aggregate finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5836,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Smooth trowel finish","answerDisplayText":"Smooth trowel finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1144,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","answerDisplayText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5463,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Salt finished","answerDisplayText":"Salt finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7044,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the location of the concrete leveling project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10540,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Finish floor in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Finish floor in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10541,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Subflooring in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Subflooring in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10542,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage or basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage or basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10543,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10544,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exterior walkway/patio","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway/patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10545,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10546,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10540,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Finish floor in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Finish floor in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10541,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Subflooring in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Subflooring in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10542,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage or basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage or basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10543,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10544,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exterior walkway/patio","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway/patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10545,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10546,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4053,"questionDisplayText":"Damage Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the damage to your concrete?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2972,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Heaving","answerDisplayText":"Heaving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5593,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Settling","answerDisplayText":"Settling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1702,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cracking","answerDisplayText":"Cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2972,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Heaving","answerDisplayText":"Heaving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5593,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Settling","answerDisplayText":"Settling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1702,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cracking","answerDisplayText":"Cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4054,"questionDisplayText":"Special Applications","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Does the concrete being repaired have any special applications or finishes?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5930,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","answerDisplayText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3607,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lightweight concrete","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2303,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exposed aggregate finish","answerDisplayText":"Exposed aggregate finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5836,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Smooth trowel finish","answerDisplayText":"Smooth trowel finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1144,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","answerDisplayText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5463,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Salt finished","answerDisplayText":"Salt finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5930,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","answerDisplayText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3607,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lightweight concrete","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2303,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exposed aggregate finish","answerDisplayText":"Exposed aggregate finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5836,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Smooth trowel finish","answerDisplayText":"Smooth trowel finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1144,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","answerDisplayText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5463,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Salt finished","answerDisplayText":"Salt finished","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40195/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40195,"taskName":"Concrete - Injection Leveling - Mudjacking","taskDescription":"Level Concrete Slabs Using Injection Technology","xmTaskDescriptor":"Mudjackers \u0026 Concrete Leveling Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":288,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"concrete leveling injection mud injection","textMessagingName":"Concrete Inj Level","rolloverLongDesc":"Liquid concrete is injected under the old slab using precise techniques to raise the slab until it is level or slightly sloped at the correct angle. Also called mudjacking. Mostly used in commercial applications. For most residential uses, out-of-level slabs are typically broken up \u0026 replaced.","rolloverShortDesc":"Injecting liquid concrete beneath slab to level.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Mudjack or Level Concrete Slabs Using Injection Technology.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated mudjacking and concrete leveling contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Mudjacking \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Concrete Leveling, Driveway Injection, Mudjackers","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Concrete Leveling \u0026 Mudjacking","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Concrete - Injection Leveling - Mudjacking","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Concrete Leveling or Mudjacking Project","urlName":"Concrete-Driveways-Patios-and-Walks-Injection-Leveling","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Mudjacking Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Concrete Leveling, Cost, Driveway Injection","searchKeywords":"concrete,leveling,injection,mud,injection,jacking,mudjacking,slabjacking, mud, jacking","emcCategoryOid":-12015,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":502,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}